[
    {
        "qid": 1068278,
        "question": "Patient is a 9 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, thyroid cartilage, and pharynx.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option4": "Epiglottitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "79%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 759301,
        "question": "Patient is a 53 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the thyroid cartilage, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option4": "Unstable angina",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "86%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1152656,
        "question": "Patient is a 50 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or feels palpitations.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "51%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 513585,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option2": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 212278,
        "question": "Patient is a 74 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has recently had a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "70%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 904900,
        "question": "Patient is a 1 year old female.<br>- The patient has had significantly increased sweating.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and heavy.<br>- The patient feels pain in their left temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located at a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.",
        "option1": "Acute otitis media",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Chagas",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "81%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 1156316,
        "question": "Patient is a 49 year old female.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has recently had a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "option2": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "50%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1122013,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a knife stroke.<br>- The patient feels pain on the right side of the chest and the left breast.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has noticed new fatigue, generalized and vague discomfort, diffuse muscle aches, or a change in their general well-being related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Anemia",
        "option2": "Myocarditis",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 610248,
        "question": "Patient is a 12 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option2": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Anaphylaxis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "88%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 833017,
        "question": "Patient is a 17 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the left side of the chest and the right breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is located with a precision of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "59%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 232398,
        "question": "Patient is a 44 year old male.<br>- The patient's nose or the back of their throat is itchy.<br>- The patient has severe itching in one or both eyes.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Cluster headache",
        "option2": "Acute otitis media",
        "option3": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "79%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 115062,
        "question": "Patient is a 7 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, under the jaw, and in the trachea.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option4": "Epiglottitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "95%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 910264,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Myocarditis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 34750,
        "question": "Patient is a 7 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sharp.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 914048,
        "question": "Patient is a 37 year old female.<br>- The patient's nose or the back of their throat is itchy.<br>- The patient has severe itching in one or both eyes.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Cluster headache",
        "option2": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "option3": "Acute otitis media",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]